Guide to the Francis C. Moon papers, 1961-2009.
Moon, Francis C. papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Francis C. Moon papers, 1961-2007.
16-5-4047
Moon, F. C.,
11 cubic feet.
Photographs, movie film, publications, research materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Files of research publications and reports; research reports; patents; VHS videotapes of research experiments.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Francis Charles Moon is the Joseph C. Ford Professor of Mechanical Engineering, Emeritus. He was the Director of the Sibley School of Mechanical and Aerospace Engineering at Cornell University from 1987 to 1992. Prior to that, he chaired the Dept. of Theoretical and Applied Mechanics from 1980 to 1987. He taught courses in Chaotic Vibration, Chaotic Dynamics, and Kinetic Sculpture. He also published a textbook on Applied Dynamics. He made contributions to the field of nonlinear and chaotic dynamics of mechanical systems and has written on Chaotic Vibrations, Chaotic and Fractal Dynamics, Dynamics and Chaos in Manufacturing Processes, Superconducting Levitation, and Magneto-Solid Mechanics. He holds patents for a non-contacting levitated rotor-bearing assembly. Most recently, he has been interested in the history of machines, particularly the history of kinematics of machines.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Files of research publications and reports; research reports; patents; VHS videotapes of research experiments, etc.; drawings and artwork for books; film clips of Mag-Lev technology (16mm); notes and videos for kinetic sculpture course; files from his director and chair positions; Mag-Lev transportation conference proceedings and National Research Council reports; research photographs and slides; and magnetic fusion superconducting magnet design reports.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Moon, F. C., 1939-; Cornell University -- Faculty.; Sibley School of Mechanical and Aerospace Engineering.; Sibley School of Mechanical and Aerospace Engineering. Department of Theoretical and Applied Mechanics.
Subjects:
Magnetic levitation.; Chaotic behavior in systems.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
See also Francis Charles Moon Reuleaux Reference Collection, #6960.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Research Reports
Series II. Publications
Series III. Patents
Series IV. Photographs and Slides
Series V. Videos
Kinetic Sculpture Course Videos
Series VI. Drawings for Publications
Series VII. Director of Sibley School of Mechanical and Aerospace Engineering and Chair of the Department of Theoretical and Applied Mechanics Documents
Series VIII. 16mm Films
Series IX. Mag-Lev Transportation Conference Proceedings
Series X. Kinetic Sculpture Course Files
Series XI. Mag-Lev Research and Reports
Series XII. Magnetic Fusion Superconducting Magnet Design Reports
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Research Reports
  - A Theory for High Current Elastic Conductors, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Effect of Stress-Wave Diffraction on Stress Measurements and a Concept for an Omnidirectional Dynamic Stress Gage, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Wave Propagation in a Composite Material Containing Dispersed Rigid Spherical Inclusions, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Anisotropic Ultrasonic Wave Propagation in a Nematic Liquid Crystal Placed in a Magnetic Field, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Propagation of Elastic Waves in Periodic Fiber Composite Materials, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Vibrations of Current Carrying Plates, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Wave Surfaces Due to Impact on Anisotropic Fiber Composite Plates, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Magnetically Induced Stress Waves in a one-Dimensional Conducting Solid, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Buckling of a Dielectric Fiber in an Electric Field, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Magtrack-Surface Transportation for the 80's, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Theoretical Analysis of Impact Composite Plates Part 1, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Stress Wave Calculations in Composite Plates Using the Fast Fourier Transform, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Application of Feedback Control to the Suppression of a Dynamic Instability of an Elastic Body, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Recent Experimental and Theoretical Progress on the Vibrations of Elastic Structures in Magnetic Fields, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Theoretical Analysis of Impact in Composite Plates, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - A Critical Survey of Wave Propagation and Impact in Composite materials, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Princeton Joint Solid Waste Management Study Committee Findings and Conclusions, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Vibration and Stability of a Set Superconducting Toroidal Magnets, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Vibration and Stability of a Set Superconducting Toroidal Magnets, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Mechanics of Structures with High Electric Currents, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Analysis of Edge Impact Stresses in Composite Plates, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Negative Damping Forces and Stresses in a Plate…, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Buckling of a Superconducting Coil Nested in a Three Coil Toroidal Segment, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Magnetoelastic Stability of Torodial Magnet Designs for Proposed Fusion Reactors, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Study of Optimum Layup Angle in Multilayer Composite Plate Under Impact, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Impact of Composite Plates, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Vibration Problems in Magnetic Levitation, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Elastic Stability and Vibration of Torodial Magnets for Fusion Reactors, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Magnetoelastic Stability and Vibrations of Superconducting Magnets, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Analysis of Stresses and Forces Due to Impact of Composite Plates, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Elastic Stability and Vibrations of Superconducting Magnets for Magnetic Fusion Reactors, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Impact of Composite Plates: Analysis of Stresses and Forces, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Static and Dynamic Instabilities in Mag-lev Model Experiments, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lateral Buckling and Vibrations of Superconducting Magnets for Magnetic Fusion Reactors, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Should a Feasibility Study be Conducted for a Municipal Electric Distribution System?, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Impact on Multilayered Composite Plates (B. S. Kim), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Transport Wihout Wheels, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Pulsed Magneto-thermal Crack Detection Using an Infrared Scanner, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Fiber Optic Cable Survivability Testing, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Nonconservative Instabilities in Electrodynamic Magnetic Levitation of Vehicles, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Infrared Measurments of Induced Eddy Currents in Sheet Conductors, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Detection of Vibrations in Metallic Structures Using Small Passive Magnetic Fields, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Numerical Solutions for Coupled Magnetomechanics, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Buckling Induced Stresses in Martensitic Stainless Steels for Magnetic Fusion Reactors, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Dynamics of Fiber Optic Cable Payout, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Magnetically Induced Cylindrical Stress Waves in a Thermoelastic Conductor, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Two Papers on Eddy Current Calculations in Thin Plates, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Eddy Current Flows Around Cracks in Thin Plates for Nondestructive Testing, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - The Virial Theorem and Scaling Laws for Superconducting Magnet Systems, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Finite Element Analysis of Coupled Magnetomechanical Problems of Conducting Plates, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Hall Potential Effects on Eddy Currents in Metals at Cryogenic Temperatures, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Finite Element Analysis of Vibration of Torodial Field Coils Coupled with Laplace Transform, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Magnetoelastic Instabilities and Vibrations of Superconducting Magnet Systems, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - A Boundary Integral Method for Eddy Current Flow around Cracks in Thin Plates (3), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Electromagnetic Tip Blunting and Increased Fracture Resistance in Thin Plates, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Magnetomechanics and Fracture, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Fractal Chaos Criterion for a Forced Two-State Oscillator, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Pre- and Post-Processing for Stream-Function Eddy Current Calculations, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - The Fractal Dimension of the Two-Well Potential Strange Attractor, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Parametric Stiffness Control of Flexible Structures, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Stability Analysis of a Robotic Mechanism Using Computer Algebra, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Magnetoelastic Instabilities in Superconducting Structures and Earnshaw's Theorem, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Double Poincare Sections of a Quasi-Periodically Forced, Chaotic Attractor, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Teaching Engineering Analysis Using Symbolic Algebra and Calculus, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Fractal Basin Boundries in a Two-Degree-of-Freedom Nonlinear System, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Fractal Basin Boundries and Homoclinic Orbits for Periodic Motion in a Two-Well Potential, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Evidence for Homoclinic Orbits as a Precursor to Chaos in a Magnetic Pendulum, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Chaotic Dynamics of a Nonlinear Servo Device with Linear Feedback Control, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - New Research Directions for Chaotic Phenomena in Solid Mechanics, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Divergence, Flutter and Strange Attractors in Magnetically Levitated Vehicles, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - An Optical Technique for Measuring Fractal Dimensions of Planar Poincare Maps, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Chaotic Motion of an Elastic-Plastic Beam, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Multiple Homoclinic Bifurcation Criteria for Chaos for a Two-Degree of Freedom Oscillator, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Superconductivity and Mechanical Engineering, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Superconducting Bearing Research, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Technical Impact of New Superconductors on Mag-Lev Transportation, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Nonlinear Dynamics and Control of Flexible Structures, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Laminated Piezopolymer Plates For Torsion…, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - High-Tc Superconducting Bearing Research at Cornell, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Comparison of Passive Superconducting Bearings with Conventional Bearing Systems, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Empirical Dry-Friction Modeling in a Forced Oscillator Using Chaos, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Spatio-Temporal Chaos in a Vibrating String with Nonlinear Amplitude Constraints, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Experimental Vibration Suppression in a Space Truss Using Self-Equilibrated Colocated Feedback Control, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - MAGLEV with Superconducting Permanent Magnets, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Modal Sensors/Actuators, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Experimental Study of Chaotic Vibrations in a Pin-Jointed Space Truss Structure, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Report on Trip to Three Japanese Superconductivity Laboratories: Progress in Superconducting Bearings, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Low-Temperature Measurements of Levitation Forces in YBa2Cu3O7; 4.2 K to 77 K, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Phenomenology of Forces Acting Between Magnets and Superconductors, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Measurement of Levitation Forces in Bulk YBa2Cu3O7 in a High Magnetic Field, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Research and Development on High Temperature Superconducting Magnetic Bearing, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Machine Engineering in the 1990's: Implications for Education and Research, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - High Tc Superconducting Magnetic Bearings in High Speed Rotor, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Dynamic Buckling in Large Structures, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Nonlinear Dynamics and Control of Flexible Structures, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Superconducting Bearing Research, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Control and Chaos, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Levitation Forces in Bulk YBCO in a High Magnetic Field and Low Temperatures, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Thickness Effect of Levitation Forces in a Bulk Melt-Quenched YBa2Cu3O7 Superconductor, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Progress in High Temperature Superconducting Bearings, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Nonlinear Dynamics Research in the Former Soviet Union, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Superconducting Bearings for High Load Applications, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Solitary Deformation Patterns in the Parametrically Driven Elastica, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Grain-Size Dependance of Levitation Forces in Bulk YBa2Cu3O7 Superconductors, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Transition from Soliton to Chaotic Motion During Impact, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Superconducting Bearing Research, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Nonlinear Dynamics of Deployable and Maneuverable Space Structures, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Nonlinear Dynamics of Deployable and Maneuverable Space Structures, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Nonlinear Dynamics of Deployable and Maneuverable Space Structures (Final Report), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Progress in Superconducting Magnetic Bearings, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Chaotic Levitated Motion of a Magnet Supported by Superconductor, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Transition From Soliton to Chaotic Motion Following Sudden Excitation of a Nonlinear Structure, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Application of Proper Orthogonal Decomposition to Dynamics of Nonlinear Structures, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Notes for System Dynamics, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - A New Method to Measure Friction Using a Chaotic Oscillator: for Paper-like Materials, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Experiments on the Use of Proper Orthogonal Decomposition to Find Principal Energy Models in Nonlinear Structures, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Numerical Studies on Dynamical Behavior of High Speed Rotor Supported by High Tc Superconducting Bearing, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Levitation Forces, Stiffness and Force-Creep in YBCO High-Tc Superconducting Thin Films, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Aspects of Passive Magnetic Levitation Based on High-Tc Superconducting YBCO Thin Films, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Amplitude-Dependent Magnetic Stiffness of Melt Quenched YBa2Cu3O7-δ Superconductors, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Levitation Drift of a Magnet and High Temperature Superconductor System in Alternative Magnetic Field, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Actuation Scheme for Controlling Vibration in a Small Commercial Lathe, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Solitions, Chaos, and Modal Interactions in Periodic Structures, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Modeling of a Cable Actuated Elastica Manipulator, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Nonlinear Dynamics and Material Processing and Manufacturing, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - What Happened to Maglev Amtrak?, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Chaotic Motions in Normal Cutting of Metals, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - A Magneto-elastic Oscillator with Delay Preliminary Experiments, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Hybrid Superconducting Bearing, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - A Study on Chaotic Levitated Motion of High-Tc Superconducting Bearing -Multi-Fractal to Chaotic Vibration and Hysteresis-, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - A Nonlinear Analysis of Models for Coupled Oscillators in Fluid Flow, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Chaotic Dynamics in Scribing Polycarbonate Plates with a Diamond Cutter, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - M.Eng. Report Hybrid Superconducting Bearing, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Nonlinear Tools for Characterizing Pre-Chatter and Chatter Vibrations in the Machining of Metals, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bifurcations, Quasiperiodicity and Chaos in Machine Tool Vibrations, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Experimental Evidence of Quasiperiodicity and Chaos in a Mechanical System with Delay, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - IUTAM Chaos '97: Applications of Nonlinear and Chaotic Dynamics in Mechanics, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Applied Mechanics in Science and Engineering (Pao), 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Helical Waves and Non-Linear Dynamics of Fluid/Structure Interactions in a Tube Row, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - A New Nonlinear System Indentification Methodology, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - A Comparison Between Direct and Indirect Friction Measurements in a Forced Oscillator, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Regenerative Machine Tool Oscillations, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - An Investigation of Nonlinear Models for a Cylinder Row in a Cross Flow, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Reflections on Nonlinear Dynamics of Machines and Structures, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Nonlinear Dynamics in Material Processing Research in the United States, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Progress in Nonlinear and Chaotic Dynamics of Structures, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - American Academy of mechanics/National Science Foundation Workshop Biographies and Pre-Workshop Reports, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Nonlinear Dynamics and Control of Large Arrays of Coupled Oscillators: Application to Fluid-Elastic Problems, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Future Research Directions in Solid Mechanics, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - History of Machines and Mechanisms, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Modeling of a Cable Actuated Elastica Manipulator, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - A Compendium of Research and Historical Artifact Collections at Cornell University, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Series II. Publications
  - "The Rigid Inclusion in a Non-Symmetrc Field", 1966 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - "The Influence of the Curvature of Spherical Waves on Dynamic Stress Concentration", 1967 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - "Interactions of Point Defects and Elastic Inclusions", 1967 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - "Magnetoelastic Buckling of a Thin Plate", 1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - "A Theory for High-Current Elastic Conductors", 1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - "A Brief History of Variational Principles in Mechanics", 1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - "Vibration and Dynamic Instability of a Beam-Plate in a Transverse Magnetic Field", 1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - "The Mechanics of Ferroelastic Plates in a Uniform Magnetic Field", 1970 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "The Control of Flutter Instability in a Continuous Elastic System Using Feedback", 1970 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "Scattering of Waves by a Cylindrical Piezoelectric Inclusion", 1970 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "Effect of Diffraction on Stress-Wave Measurement and a Concept for an Omnidirectional-Dynamic-Stress Gauge", 1970 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "The Mechanics of Ferroelastic Plates in a Uniform Magnetic Field", 1970 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "Propagation of Stress Waves in Fiber-Reinforced Composite Rods", 1970 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "Strumming Through History", 1970 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "The Generation of Electromagnetic Radiation by Elastic Waves", 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "Anisotropic Ultrasonic Wave Propagation in a Nematic Liquid Crystal Placed in a Magnetic Field", 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "Wave Surfaces Due to Impact on Anisotropic Plates", 1972 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "Magnetic Levitation", 1972 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "On the Scattering of Spherical Elastic Waves by a Spherical Cavity", 1972 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "The Variation of the Mechanical Properties in the Walls of Long Bones", 1972 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "One-Dimensional Transient Waves in Anisotropic Plates", 1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "Stress Wave Calculations in Composite Plates Using the Fast Fourier Transform", 1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "Elastic Stability of a Superconducting Coil for a Fusion Reactor", 1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "The Buckling of a Dielectric Fiber in an Electric Field", 1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "The Suppression of a Dynamic Instability of an Elastic Body Using Feedback Control", 1974 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "Magnetically Induced Stress Waves in a Conducting Solid-Theory and Experiment", 1974 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "Laboratory Studies of Magnetic Levitation in the Thin Track Limit", 1974 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "Dynamic Interaction Between a Linear Induction Motor and Elastic Reaction Rail", 1974 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "Wave Propagation and Impact in Composite Materials", 1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "Elastic Vibrations Due to a High-current Arc Discharge", 1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "Magneto-Elastic Stability of Toroidal Magnet Designs for Proposed Fusion Reactors", 1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "Magnetoelastic Buckling and Vibration of a Rod Carrying Electric Current", 1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "Buckling of a Superconducting Coil Nested in a Three-Coil Toroidal Segment", 1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "Vibration and Stability of a Set of Superconducting Toroidal Magnets", 1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "Transient Wave Propagation in Composite Plates Due to Impact", 1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "Buckling and Vibrations in a Five-Coil Superconducting Partial Torus", 1977 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "An Eight Coil Superconducting Torus for Elastic Buckling Studies", 1977 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "Experiments on Buckling and Vibration of Superconducting Coils", 1977 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "Magnetic Levitation of Trains and Related Possibilities in Magneto-Mechanics", 1977 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "Magnetoelastic Buckling of a Superconducting Energy Storage Shell", 1977 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "Vibration Problems in Magnetic Levitation and Propulsion", 1977 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "The Coupled Response of a Dynamic Element Riding on a Continuously Supported Beam", 1978 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - "Active Feedback Control of a Beam Subjected to a Nonconservative Force", 1978 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - "Problems in Magneto-solid Mechanics", 1978 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - "Buckling of a Superconducting Ring in a Toroidal Magnetic Field", 1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - "Experiments on Magnetoelastic Buckling in a Superconducting Torus", 1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - "Impact Induced Stress Waves inan Anisotropic Plate", 1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - "A Magnetoelastic Strange Attractor", 1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - "Experiments on Chaotic Motions of a Forced Nonlinear Oscillator: Strange Attractors", 1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - "Experimental Models for Strange Attractor Vibrations in Elastic Systems", 1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - "Elastic Vibrations and Waves in a Superconducting Torus", 1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - "Magnetoelastic Instabilities in Superconducting Structures and Earnshaw's Theorem", 1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - "Magnetically Induced Cylindrical Stress Waves in a Thermoelastic Conductor", 1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "Magnetic Forces in Plates Using Finite Elements", 1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "Elastic Buckling of Superconducting Yin-Yang Magnets for Fusion", 1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "Misalignment Sensitivity of Solenoid Magnets for MFTF-B and Tandem-Mirror Next Step Facility", 1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "Eddy Current Calculations in Thin Conducting Plates Using a Finite Element-Stream Function Code", 1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "Buckling Induced Stresses in martensitic Stainless Steels for Magnetic Fusion Reactors", 1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "Eddy Currents Around Cracks in Thin Plates Due to a Current Filament", 1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "Eddy Current Flows Around Cracks in Thin Plates for Nondestructive Testing", 1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "The Virial Theorem and Scaling Laws for Superconducting Magnet Systems", 1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "Finite Element Analysis of Large Scale Superconducting Toroidal Field Coil Coupled With Laplace Transform", 1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "Chaotic Vibrations of a Beam with Non-Linear Boundary Conditions", 1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "Observations of Dynamic Instabilities in Magnetically Levitated Models", 1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "Dynamic Instabilities in Magnetically Levitated Models", 1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "Strange Attractors and Chaos in Nonlinear Mechanics", 1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)